Ever since that accident,
自從發生那場意外後
I've been able to hear the thoughts of anyone I locked eyes with.
我就變得能夠聽到 與我目光交會的人的心聲
I'm Yun Tae-o.
我是尹泰晤
I'm 26 years old. I came to Japan almost two years ago.
來到日本快滿兩年，26歲
When he talks, it's in Japanese.
說話的時候是講日語…
But his thoughts are…
但他在心裡
…in Korean.
是講韓語
Excuse me.
我先走了
-I want you to meet our new intern. -Oh, sure.
-我想介紹今天新來的實習生 -啊，好的
Come in.
進來吧
Huh? Yuri?
什麼？侑里小姐？
I knew we'd meet again.
我們果然又見面了
What? No one told me about this.
為什麼？我沒聽說這件事
HR was always my responsibility.
人事不是都由我負責嗎？
Oh, that's right.
是啊，你說得對
This is our CEO, Yuri Motomiya.
這位是本宮侑里，是我們的社長
What? Yuri is the CEO?
什麼？侑里小姐是社長？
Are you really the CEO?
社長？真的假的？
Do you two know each other?
你們兩個認識嗎？
Or rather, we're…
與其說是認識…
Yes, we're good friends.
是的，我們感情很好
Yes, I'm fully charged.
是的，現在能量滿滿
Cute.
真可愛
I'm happy I got to see you.
能見到你，我很開心
No, he's just a deliveryman who brings food to me.
不，他只是幫我送餐到府的外送員
That's all.
就只是這樣而已
Really?
是喔
Then, you might know already, but he's Mr. Yun Tae-o.
那你可能已經知道了 他是尹泰晤先生
His school connected us, and he'll work here until he graduates in two months.
是經由研究所介紹 到畢業為止的兩個月期間
Then, if everything goes smoothly,
之後如果沒有任何問題
we'll sign him on.
我就會正式錄用他
If everything goes smoothly…
“如果沒有任何問題”…
If everything goes smoothly.
如果沒任何問題的話就會那樣做
We don't need workers who mix up their work and private life.
我們公司不需要公私不分的人
Now, let me introduce you to the team.
那我還要把你介紹給團隊成員
-What are you doing? -Nothing.
-你在做什麼？ -沒什麼
You can go now.
快點去吧
I'm Yun Tae-o, 26 years of age, and I came to Japan almost two years ago.
我是尹泰晤，來日本快滿兩年 今年26歲
Nice to meet you.
請多多指教
-He's glowing. -His legs are so long.
-他好耀眼哪 -腿好長
Mr. Yun is…
關於尹先生…
Please call me Tae-o.
叫我泰晤就好
So, Tae-o…
這位泰晤…
-Sea otters, right? -Yes.
-你之前是說海獺對嗎？ -是的
He's studying endangered animals,
由於他正在研究瀕臨絕種的動物
so I'd like to put him in charge of the upcoming seminar project.
我想將今後準備開設的 講座類企劃交給他負責
But we'll start you off with basic work as an assistant.
不過我會先讓他從 基本的助手工作開始
All right! Is he my assistant?
好耶！是我的助手嗎？
He'll be with Nishina for now.
我打算讓他暫時跟著仁科小姐
Oh, okay.
好，知道了
You speak Korean, right?
仁科小姐會說韓語吧？
A little.
只會一點點
You can speak Korean?
你會說韓語啊？
I've been there a few times.
我去過韓國幾次
And I have a few friends.
也有幾位韓國人朋友
That's great.
太好了
-I look forward to working with you. -Me too.
-請多指教 -彼此彼此
It's nothing.
沒事
Are you hungry, Yuri?
侑里小姐，你肚子餓了嗎？
-"Yuri"?
-“侑里小姐”？
It's not like that.
不是那樣的
They know each other.
他們兩人好像認識
-Did he get in through connections? -No.
-他是走後門進來的嗎？ -不是的
It's a coincidence. Really.
只是剛好，真的是碰巧認識
A coincidence…
碰巧…
How do you know each other?
你們是什麼關係？
Well…
這個嘛…
-I'd bring food… -Food?
-我經常送飯… -送飯？
-Yeah, food. -I'd go "ding ding."
-對，就是送飯 -我負責“噗嚕…”
-Yeah, ding ding. -Ding?
-對，噗嚕… -“噗嚕”？
-Ding… -Um, delivery.
-噗嚕… -那個，就是外送
Yes, he worked part-time as a delivery boy and brought me food.
對，他兼差做外送員 曾經幫我送餐，就只是這樣
-I see.
-原來如此
-Are you done? -Yes.
-講完了嗎？ -講完了
Anyway, I want Tae-o to work hard
總之我會以正式錄用為前提
as an intern who is set to become a full-time employee.
讓他暫時以實習生的身分 好好學習這裡的工作
So give him your full support as well.
所以請各位也幫一下他
-Okay.
-好的
Nishina, show him his desk.
那仁科小姐，請帶他到座位上
Okay.
好的
Tae-o, your seat is over here.
泰晤，你的位子在這裡
Thank you.
謝謝
And get a grip, Motomiya.
本宮，你要振作一點
Got it?
知道嗎？
Of course.
當然知道
We don't need workers who mix up their work and private life.
我們公司不需要公私不分的人
What? You're rejecting them?
什麼？要拒絕嗎？
P.S. HOW ABOUT DINNER?
（備註，改天一起吃飯）
Even if they're a client,
就算對方是客戶
we can't trust people like this.
在工作中夾帶私情的人我無法信任
That's true, but…
是沒錯啦…
We don't need workers who mix up their work and private life.
我們公司不需要公私不分的人
Be careful, Motomiya.
你也要多注意點
What?
什麼？
Be careful.
我叫你多留意
Okay.
好
If anything happens, he could even fire me, the CEO.
要是出什麼事 連我這個社長都可能會被他開除
Yuri.
侑里小姐
Please stop being like this.
請你不要再這樣做了
Please treat me like your boss at the office.
在公司請跟我保持上司及下屬的關係
Why?
為什麼？
Hanaoka told you too, right?
花岡也跟你說過吧？
If things go smoothly, you sign with us.
如果沒有引起問題才會正式錄用你
Hanaoka doesn't go easy on people.
他是毫不留情的人
He'll cut out anyone who mixes work and private affairs.
公私不分的人馬上就會被他開除
Private…
公私…
People who can't keep their work and private life separate.
是指無法區別工作和私生活的意思
So, please don't talk to me at the office unless it's work-related.
所以在公司裡 除了工作內容以外不要來向我攀談
Even so, I'm happy I get to see you every day.
但我還是覺得很開心 因為每天都能見到侑里小姐
And…
而且…
We're outside the office now.
這裡是公司外
It's basically the office.
跟公司沒什麼兩樣
Could it be that you're mad?
你該不會是在生氣吧？
I am.
沒錯
Oh, you must be hungry.
我知道了，你肚子餓了啊
Let's eat.
一起吃飯吧
I told you, I'm not eating with you anymore.
所以說，我們不能一起吃飯了
I really won't.
真的不能一起吃飯
Why does he have to work under me?
為什麼他偏偏是我的下屬？
Hey, Tae-o… Sir.
對了，泰晤先生
Yes?
是
My kid replied when I sent your photo.
咱把跟泰晤的合照 傳給女兒看，她回覆我了
-That's rare. -Yeah, it's been six months.
-真難得 -對，她半年沒回了
My daughter's a fan of K-pop.
咱女兒很喜歡韓國流行樂
I know this isn't much of a thanks,
雖然這稱不上是謝禮
but here.
這送你
Is this jogi?
這是“jogi”嗎？
-From where? -I bought it in Shin-Okubo yesterday!
-怎麼突然買這個？ -咱昨天去新大久保買的！
How do you eat that?
那是要怎麼吃啊？
Thank you.
謝謝
You're such a nice person, Mr. Kamei.
龜井先生是個大好人耶
Don't be a stranger.
別那麼客氣啦
You can just call me Kame.
可以叫“阿龜”就好
-Good morning.
-早安
Yuri, good morning.
侑里小姐，早安
Did you eat?
-吃早餐了嗎？ -請你別再管我有沒有吃飯了
Looks tasty.
看起來真美味
I'm going to grill this later.
晚點把它烤來吃吧
Can you look over the Strawberry Farm contract?
你確認一下草莓農園的合約書
-Got it. -Okay.
-知道了 -好
-You're okay, right? -Yes.
-你真的沒問題吧？ -沒問題
You're clearly acting strange since Tae-o came, Motomiya.
自從泰晤來了之後 你明顯變得很奇怪，本宮
I'm completely fine.
我跟平時一樣啊
-If you say so. -Yeah.
-那就好 -好
How is he that perceptive?
他為何如此敏銳啊？
To increase our e-commerce profits, we'll change our posts
為了提高電子商務平台的營收
to match the algorithms.
投稿時要更注重演算法
Yeah, the taste and design are important,
是啊，除了味道和設計外
but let's be more proactive about sharing our initiatives.
我們要更積極地宣傳我們的理念
-Okay. -Good.
-好的 -很好
Lunch is here.
午餐送到了
-Oh, thanks. -Thank you.
-哦，謝謝 -謝謝
-Fried rice and babaocai. -Great, thanks.
-有炒飯、八寶菜 -好，謝謝
-Tae-o. -Yes, thank you.
-泰晤
-Mapo tofu for Boss. -Thanks.
-社長的是麻婆豆腐 -謝謝
The restaurant recommended the extra spicy one.
這是店家推薦的超辣口味喔
-Chili shrimp? -Me.
-乾燒明蝦是誰的？ -我的
-Hanaoka and Kame. -Thanks.
-龜先生和花岡先生 -謝謝
Here, Boss.
來，社長
Thank you.
謝謝
You don't like babaocai?
泰晤不喜歡八寶菜嗎？
I do.
喜歡
But Yuri can't have anything too spicy.
但是侑里小姐不敢吃太辣的
Oh, you knew because I never ordered any spicy food, right?
啊，因為我叫外送時都不會點辣的嘛
You have a great memory, Tae-o.
泰晤先生的記憶力真好
Why does Boss act so formal around Tae-o?
社長為什麼只對泰晤用敬語？
You sure are amazing, Tae-o.
泰晤真是厲害呀
I'm so tired of this.
好難熬
Huh? What's the matter?
什麼？你怎麼啦？
Oh, Yuri?
啊，侑里小姐？
Yuri, thank God.
是侑里小姐，太好了
Why are you soaking wet?
你為何全身溼透了？
Um…
那個…
come with me.
跟我來
What? I told you, I can't.
什麼？我就說不可以了
There's water coming from above.
水從上面灑下來了
What?
什麼啊？
Well…
那個…
Calm down.
你冷靜一點
Wait.
停下來
I don't understand!
我聽不懂！
When you grill fish, the sprinklers will go off if you don't run the ventilator.
烤魚的時候要打開換氣扇 不然灑水器就會啟動
Be careful.
要多注意喔
Okay. I sincerely apologize.
好的，真的非常抱歉
I apologize.
非常抱歉
It'll take about two days to clean the room,
清掃房屋大概需要兩天的時間
so figure out your own lodging during that time, okay?
這段期間要住哪就麻煩自己安排喔
Yes, sir.
好的
I'm sorry.
對不起
Should we find you a hotel?
怎麼辦？要找間旅館嗎？
It's gotten late, so I'll ask my professor to let me stay over.
現在已經很晚了 我想請老師讓我借宿
Professor?
老師？
My professor at the research lab.
他是我研究所的教授
He didn't pick up.
他沒有接電話
Are you okay?
還好嗎？
Hello, Iiyama lab.
你好，這裡是飯山研究室
Senpai, I can't get in touch with the professor.
學長，我聯絡不到老師
He's on a work trip in Hokkaido.
教授去北海道出差了
Then please let me stay at your house.
那我能借住在學長家嗎？
Sure. When?
可以啊，什麼時候？
Right now.
現在
I can't right now.
現在沒辦法耶
I'm observing the black hagfish.
我正在觀察黑黏盲鰻，無法抽身
You don't have to be there. Just give me the key.
學長不在也沒關係，借我鑰匙就好
What?
什麼？
How was it?
怎麼樣？
It was no good.
行不通
Thank you for this.
謝謝你借我這個
No problem.
不客氣
Is this basically the office too?
這裡也幾乎算是公司嗎？
This is…
這裡…
Basically…
幾乎算是…
I'm doing this as a boss for my employee.
我是以社長的身分照顧公司員工…
As an employee, for my boss.
我是以員工的身分照顧社長…
As an employee, for… What? No!
以員工的身分？社長？不對啦！
Yuri?
侑里小姐
Did you fall asleep?
你已經睡了嗎？
What do I do?
怎麼辦？
I don't want to wake her.
我不想吵醒她
Yuri!
侑里小姐！
I'm sorry!
對不起！
Are you okay?
你沒事吧？
I've never done this before!
我是第一次這樣！
Never done what before?
什麼事情第一次？
I fell from the bed. That's all.
我只是從床上跌下來而已
Did you fall from the bed? That's cute.
從床上掉下來了？真可愛
Is something the matter?
怎麼了嗎？
My suit is wrinkled.
我的西裝皺巴巴的
It's fine if you wear casual wear.
你穿便服就好了
We don't have a dress code.
我們公司沒有規定服裝要怎麼穿
I appreciate it.
真是過意不去啊
Here.
請用
You know "Gamsahabnida," huh?
你知道“Gamsahabnida”呀？
Yeah, but that's all I know.
對，但我就只會這句
That, and "annyeonghaseyo."
再來就只有“Annyeonghaseyo”
"Hello" and "Thank you," huh?
“你好”和“謝謝”，對吧？
Xie xie.
“謝謝”
Khop khun kha. Merci.
“Khop khun kha”、“Merci”
Gracias.
“Gracias”
What is that?
是什麼意思？
I realized we know hello and thank you
我只是在想就算不懂其他國家的語言
in quite a few languages even if we may not speak them.
至少還是知道如何打招呼 以及“謝謝”怎麼說
I think it's kind of wonderful that the word we know is "Thank you."
廣為人知的話是“謝謝” 感覺是很美好的一件事
I like that side of you.
我就喜歡你這一點
But there's one more.
但是還有一句話
Besides saying hello and thank you,
除了“你好”和“謝謝”之外
there's a word you surely know.
還有一句大家一定都知道的話
What is it?
是什麼？
I wonder.
是什麼呢？
Yuri?
侑里小姐？
Yuri, please wait a second.
侑里小姐，等我一下啦
Like I said, you can't follow me.
就說了不可以跟著我
But it's the same place.
明明目的地都一樣
Things will get really bad if people see us come to work together.
要是被人看到我們一起上班 事情真的會一發不可收拾
Whoa, careful!
哇，很危險耶！
First, you fell from your bed,
從床上摔下來之後
and now you're getting hit by a bike?
這次換差點被腳踏車撞到？
Start walking in ten minutes.
請你十分鐘後再出發
And call me Boss at work.
還有，在公司要叫我“社長”
Wait.
停住
She's doing it again.
又來這套啊
But she's still cute.
不過還是很可愛
I told you not to follow me!
我就說不可以跟過來了！
Who did you think I was?
你誤認成誰了？
I didn't think you were anyone.
誰都不是
Almond milk isn't compatible with Japanese ingredients,
杏仁奶跟和風食材不太契合
so soy milk or rice milk might work better.
豆漿或米漿的話或許可以
I'll find a few varieties then.
那我去找幾個種類來
Thank you.
謝謝
-Right? -What?
-對吧？ -什麼啊？
Korean words?
韓語啊？
"I love you"?
“我愛你”？
Je t'aime. Saranghaeyo.
“Je t'aime”、“Saranghaeyo”
Why are you asking about Korean?
為什麼會提到韓語？
Oh, you were looking up things about Korea earlier too.
對了，你上次也在查韓語吧
It was just randomly on my mind.
只是無意中想到而已
Is that something that just randomly comes to mind?
那是無意中會想到的事情嗎？
Speaking of saranghaeyo,
說到“Saranghaeyo”
my boyfriend and I broke up.
我跟男友分手了
What? When?
什麼？何時分手的？
So, a new intern joined the company.
所以說啊，來了一個實習生對吧？
-Right? -Yes. Huh?
-對吧？ -是啊，怎麼了？
He's a great kid. He's bright, energetic, and a hard worker.
他是個很不錯的人喔 開朗活潑，工作態度也很積極
-I want to meet him soon. I'm so excited. -Why?
-好想趕快見到他，好期待 -為什麼？
I mean, he might be one of the only people I can love in this world.
因為他有可能是 我在這世上唯一的另一半啊
You can't.
那怎麼行
Why?
為什麼？
Huh?
什麼？
"Why"?
你問我原因？
Well, it would be an office romance.
因為那樣算是職場戀情
Hm? Did we have a rule against it?
什麼？我們公司有那種規定嗎？
We don't, but it's wrong when you think about it, right?
雖然沒有啦 但一般來說，這是不行的吧？
Oh, that Hanaoka guy hates stuff like that, doesn't he?
也對，像花岡先生那樣的人 感覺就很排斥那種事
Yeah.
沒錯
Exactly.
正是如此
I'll check the inventory at the store and let you know.
那等我回店裡確認庫存後再跟你聯絡
-Please do. -Okay.
-麻煩你了 -好
Oh, Yuri. Is it your lunch break?
哦，侑里小姐，你在午休嗎？
I already ate.
我已經吃過飯了
Then it's time for dessert.
那就吃甜點
What?
什麼？
Here.
請用
This is dessert?
這是甜點？
You actually haven't eaten lunch, right?
其實你還沒吃午餐吧？
How did you know?
你怎麼知道？
Because your face looks scary.
因為你的表情很恐怖
Thanks.
謝謝
Let's eat.
我開動了
Enjoy your meal.
請慢用
I'm expressing my love.
這是愛的表現
Is it good?
好吃嗎？
Yeah, it's good.
好吃，超美味
I found this in the morning.
我早上發現這個
Here's a…
送給你…
present for you, Yuri.
當禮物吧
Why?
為什麼要送我？
Yuri.
“侑里”
In Korean, Yuri means "glass."
“Yuri”在韓語中是“玻璃”的意思
Thank you.
謝謝
Yuri.
侑里
How pretty.
很漂亮
Yeah, glass is pretty.
你是說玻璃啊，的確很美
What do the kanji in your name mean?
侑里小姐名字中的漢字有什麼含意？
Oh, um…
就是…
Oh, here.
哦，等等
Someone who can help people.
成為能夠幫助他人的人
A place where people can return to.
成為某人的歸宿
It means they wanted me to become that kind of person.
名字的含意就是 希望我能成為那樣的人
That's lovely.
真棒呢
Hold on.
等我一下
Even if I look at his eyes and hear his thoughts,
就算眼睛看著他、會聽見他的心聲
I don't have to worry about it.
仍可以自在地相處
I've never met someone like that.
我是第一次遇到這樣的人
-Here. -I need a lot more.
-來 -我要更多
Being with this person whose thoughts I can't read
跟這個讀不懂內心話的人在一起
puts me at ease, and I enjoy it.
我感到無比輕鬆，而且好快樂
-Tae-o. -Yes?
-泰晤 -是
Why'd you become an intern at our company?
你為什麼會來我們公司實習？
It's thanks to my professor.
都是多虧我的老師
Your professor at grad school, right?
老師是指你的教授嗎？
When I was a kid,
在我小的時候
he was doing research at a university in Korea.
老師在韓國的大學做研究
He lived next door and often played with me.
他就住在我家隔壁，經常陪我玩
This is a sea otter? It's so cute!
這就是海獺嗎？好可愛！
What is it in Japanese?
日語要怎麼說？
-A rakko. -Rakko?
-“Rakko” -“Rakko”？
Rakko.
“Rakko”
There aren't many, but you can see them in the wild in Japan.
在日本雖然數量很少 但還是能看到野生的海獺
I'll take you there one day.
有機會我帶你去看吧
Hooray!
太好了！
I'm home.
我回來了
-Welcome home.
-回來啦
Thanks, Iiyama. Did you eat?
飯山先生，謝謝你，你吃飯了嗎？
Now that you mention it, I didn't eat anything today.
這麼說起來，我今天都還沒吃東西呢
That's no good.
這樣怎麼行
You need to get energized!
要好好補給一下能量！
I'll help you, ma'am.
伯母，我也來幫忙吧
No, it's okay.
不用啦，你別介意
Iiyama, please teach me about sea otters.
飯山叔叔，告訴我海獺的事情嘛
Tae-o.
泰晤
It'll be okay.
沒事的
When you feel lonely,
感到寂寞的時候
you shouldn't be alone.
別獨自一人待著
Tae-o,
泰晤
do you want to go to Japan with me?
你要不要跟我一起去日本？
And your dad?
你爸爸呢？
My parents got divorced when I was young,
在我很小的時候，父母離婚了
so I don't know where he is.
我不知道他在哪裡
But…
不過…
the professor is my dad.
老師就像是我的爸爸
By researching with the professor in Japan…
在日本跟老師一起做研究…
I got better.
讓我恢復精神
When I felt lost about what to do after graduation,
看到畢業後感到迷惘的我
this is what the professor said.
老師對我說…
We need people who research,
雖然必須有人來做研究
but also people who give shape to those results and spread them to the world.
但也需要有人來將成果 具體化並推廣出去
I think you could do either since you are so loved by others.
總是人見人愛的泰晤 或許兩者都能達成呢
How do you spread results to the world?
想推廣出去要怎麼做才好呢？
I know several companies that do such work.
我認識幾家在做相關產業的公司
Please tell me.
請告訴我
I… I want to try it.
我想試試看
That's why I'm happy I could join your company.
所以能進入侑里小姐的公司 我真的很高興
You have your own reason for coming here, don't you.
泰晤會來到這裡有你自己的理由
What?
什麼？
Sorry.
不好意思
It's my landlord.
是房東
This is Tae-o.
我是泰晤
Really? Thank you.
真的嗎？謝謝
It seems they finished cleaning.
房屋已經清掃完畢了
That was faster than I thought.
比預期的還要早呢
-Yuri? -You can go home now.
-侑里小姐？ -你今天可以先回家
I'm sure you're busy with your room.
你還得處理房屋的事
Good work today.
辛苦了
I'm Motomiya, liberal arts.
我是綜合系的本宮
Hanaoka, you're a business major,
花岡同學，你明明是經營系的學生
but why are you always taking environmental studies classes?
卻一直來上環境系的課 這是為什麼？
I'm in the renewable energy lab,
我目前在再生能源研究室
I'm contemplating if I should go into research after graduation.
畢業後我很煩惱 是否應該繼續走研究這條路
-Why?
-為什麼？ -你問原因？
I don't know if we can fix the environment through research alone.
我在懷疑只靠研究 是否真的能改變環境問題
Environmental issues
環境問題
can potentially be fixed particularly through business.
必須靠商業手段才有辦法解決
"Business"?
商業？
Tell me more.
請你再說得詳細一些
I have my own reason for being here too.
我會在這裡也有自己的理由
"Yuri."
“侑里”
BEST BIBIMBAP EVER. I FEEL ENERGIZED. THANK YOU.
（這是我吃過最好吃的韓式拌飯 成功補給了能量，謝謝你）
It's rare for you to come right before visiting hours end.
你竟然會在會面時間結束前趕來 真難得耶
I'd be going back to an empty house.
反正回家也是一個人
Did you eat?
吃飯了嗎？
I'll eat when I get home.
回家後再吃
Delivery again?
又叫外送嗎？
No, you need a home-cooked meal once in a while.
這怎麼行，偶爾也得自己做飯啊
I've been eating home-cooked meals quite a bit lately.
我最近很常吃別人做的飯喔
-Huh? -What?
-什麼？ -怎麼了？
Who cooked for you?
誰做的飯？
What? Huh?
什麼？怎麼回事？
It's like that, is it?
是那個意思嗎？
No, it's not like that.
不是那個意思啦
And I won't be eating them anymore.
而且我已經不吃了
You won't?
不吃了？
Oh right, I bought some magazines.
對了，我隨便買了幾本書
Hot spring sommelier textbook.
《溫泉專家教課書》
Let's find the hot spring that's best for you.
來尋找適合自己的溫泉吧
Oh, thank you.
哦，謝謝你
Are you becoming a hot spring sommelier next?
這次要成為溫泉專家？
That's fine and all, but don't ask me to bring back hot spring water.
是無所謂啦 但你可別叫我帶溫泉水過來喔
I won't do it.
我不會帶的
Oh, you're here to visit Mr. Motomiya, right?
啊，你是來探望本宮先生吧？
Oh, yes.
對
Are you not going to see him again?
今天也不去見他嗎？
I just remembered something urgent.
我突然想到還有急事
-Excuse me. -I see.
-先告辭了 -好的
Yuri!
侑里！
MAHIRO HAS ADDED TAE-O TO THE GROUP CHAT
（真尋已邀請泰晤加入群組）
Why?
為什麼？
TAE-O'S WELCOME PARTY IS AT SEVEN P.M.TODAY.
（今天晚上七點 要舉辦泰晤的歡迎會）
BOSS WILL JOIN TOO!
（社長也會出席！）
Tae-o, welcome to Dolce &amp; Chocolat.!
泰晤，歡迎加入朵契與巧克力！
-Cheers!
-乾杯！
Cheers!
乾杯！
So good!
真好喝！
That's good.
真的很好喝
This is what that was about, right?
所以是這麼一回事吧？
You better thank me, Yuri.
好好感謝我喔，侑里小姐
I didn't ask for this.
真是多管閒事
Whoa, are you good at drinking?
天啊，你很能喝嗎？
Yes, I like alcohol.
是的，我喜歡喝酒
Do you as well?
前輩也是嗎？
Well, I'd say I can drink the most out of anyone here.
是啊，在這公司算是最會喝的吧
So you're the party director.
所以你就是宴會常務囉
The director?
常務？
People like you who have a strong tolerance and liven up the party
像前輩這樣很會喝酒 又很會炒熱氣氛的人
are called the party director in Korea.
在韓國我們會稱他是宴會常務
Director, huh?
常務啊？
All right, this director will teach you how to drink.
好，讓常務來教你怎麼喝酒
Tae-o, keep up.
泰晤，要跟上我喔
Yes, sir!
是，常務！
-Cheers!
-乾杯！
-Let's drink!
-喝吧！
Kame?
龜哥？
Tae-o.
泰晤
You're too strong.
你太強了哪
Director?
常務？
I'm okay.
我沒事
The director can still drink!
常務還可以繼續喝！
Are you okay?
沒事吧？
What just happened?
發生什麼事了？
Nothing. He just got drunk.
沒發生什麼事，他只是醉了
But I thought Hanaoka has only been drinking oolong tea.
可是花岡先生一直在喝烏龍茶啊
It's from earlier when this happened.
因為剛才那一杯灑出來了
What?
什麼？
He got drunk just from that?
那樣子就醉了嗎？
He can't even have a drop.
他真的一滴都不能喝
And when he gets drunk, he drops everything and leaves.
然後他每次喝醉回家都會拋下一切
That's the only cute thing about him.
他就只有那點還算可愛
Oh, Tae-o, come here.
對了，泰晤，過來這邊
Sit by me.
來姐姐旁邊
-Don't be shy. -What?
-不用害羞 -什麼？
Come on, Tae-o.
來吧，泰晤
How about we call it a night?
今天就解散吧
You can come to work in the afternoon tomorrow, so rest up.
明天可以下午再出勤 請大家好好休息
Thank you.
謝謝惠顧
MESSAGE FROM TAE-O
（泰晤傳來訊息）
Would you like to get some ice cream?
要不要去買冰淇淋？
Why ice cream?
為什麼是買冰？
IN KOREA, GETTING INVITED TO ICE CREAM MEANS HE WANTS TO BE ALONE WITH YOU!
（如果被韓國男性問要不要去買冰 他的意思就是想跟你獨處！）
HE WANTS TO BE ALONE WITH YOU. IT'S HOW MEN MAKE A MOVE!
（他的意思就是想跟你獨處！）
Here is your receipt.
這是發票，謝謝
Thank you.
謝謝
TAE-O
（泰晤）
Yuri.
侑里小姐
I found you.
找到你了
How? Where did you come from?
怎麼會？你從哪冒出來的？
Let's get ice cream.
我們去買冰淇淋吧
I will not.
我不去
I am the CEO.
我是社長
I can't get overly close with an employee.
不可以跟特定的員工 有過多不必要的接觸
Okay.
知道了
You came to our company with a goal in mind, right?
你也是為了想做的事情 而來到我們公司吧？
If anything happens, you can't sign with us.
要是有個萬一，你就不能轉正職了
Yes.
是
So…
所以…
I'm sorry.
對不起
What?
什麼？
I finally understand.
我終於明白了
You were doing this for my sake, weren't you?
侑里小姐是在為我著想吧？
I like how you usually are,
平時的侑里小姐很棒
but I like your CEO side too.
身為社長的侑里小姐也很棒
You look cool.
非常帥氣
I'm proud of you.
我為你感到自豪
Thanks.
謝謝
But that's why…
但是，所以說…
Director!
常務！
Yeah, right?
就是說啊，對吧？
I drank a lot.
我喝了滿多的
We can't let them see us, right?
不能被發現對吧？
Smell this. It's nice.
這好像有味道
That's so nice!
哇，味道好香
Just what you'd expect from Hanaoka.
不愧是花岡先生
-Let's get tonkotsu ramen. -Yeah!
-去吃豚骨拉麵吧 -好！
Keeping a boss and intern dynamic in the office is fine.
在公司，我們可以維持 社長跟實習生的關係就好
I'll only talk about work in the office.
以後在公司我只跟你談工作的事情
Instead of saying Yuri,
我不會叫“侑里小姐”
I'll call you Boss.
會叫你“社長”
Thanks.
謝謝
But in exchange, from now on,
相對的，從今以後
when we're outside,
你會在公司外
you'll make lots of time for just the two of us, right?
製造更多獨處的時間吧？
H-Hey.
總覺得啊
Are you doing this on purpose?
你是故意這樣做的？
Doing what?
什麼意思？
It's nothing.
沒什麼
But…
不過…
I'm doing this because I want you to like me.
我是希望你喜歡我，才這麼做的
What?
什麼？
After all, I'm a 26-year-old man.
畢竟我是26歲的男人
So, hurry.
所以快點…
Fall in love with me.
喜歡上我吧
What?
什麼？
Subtitle translation by: Chul Woong Kim
字幕翻譯：盧慧文
It's not like that.
不是這樣的
He acts differently with the boss.
唯獨對社長，距離感很不尋常
There's a lot of evidence here.
間接證據都湊齊了
Be careful.
小心點
You just gotta try it.
只能吃吃看
How many times?
那可以幾次？
Please go on a date with me.
請跟我約會
That's how I feel.
這是我的心意
I don't get it.
我不懂